James B. Murphy Papers ca.1918-1950 Mss.B.M956
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence, ca.1918-1950 (Box 1-39)
  - Kingsbury, Henry A
  - Kingsley, Rolfe
  - Kinney, C R
  - Kinsella, Ralph
    - World War I
  - Kiplinger, Walter C
  - Klahr, R A
  - Klats, Oskar
  - Klein, Robert J
  - Kleiner, I S
  - Knickerbocker Club
  - "Koch Trial" [Koch, William F.]
    - Bell, Gordon Knox
    - Rostenberg, Adolph, Jr.
  - Koets, P
  - Kolb, Edgar Allan
  - Kolmer, John A
  - Kopas, Joseph
  - Koppman, David
  - Kosir, Alija
  - Koster, Harry
  - Kraemer, William H
  - Krause, Allen K
  - Kroeff, Mario
  - Kroog, Henry
  - Krumbhaar, Edward B
  - Kubie, Lawrence S
  - Lacaillade, C William, Jr.
  - Lacassagne, Schram, Mildred W S
    - Schram, Mildred W S
  - Ladd, William S
    - Witt, Dan H
  - Ladeuze, P
  - Lakeman, Curtis Edmunds
  - Lamb, Albert R
  - Lamb, Henry B
  - Lambert, Robert A
  - Lamont, Mrs. John G
    - Halsted, William Stewart
  - Lamping, Jack
  - Lansdown, Mrs. Eric
  - Lange, Linda B
  - Langenbeck, Clara
    - World War I
  - Lankenau Hospital
    - Page, Henry F
    - Smith, Horace
    - Rosengarten, A G
    - Reimann, Stanley P
    - Gray, Alfred M
    - Walker, Theresa Fox
  - Lansdown, Mrs. Frances
    - Dochez, R A
    - Stewart, Harold
    - Lincoln, Asa
  - Larkin, Harold
    - Brackett, Elizabeth
  - Lasher, Arthur F
  - Lassiter, Ben J
  - Lathrope Mouse Records
    - Gray, Mrs. A W
    - Barret, Harvey P
    - James, Henry
    - Robson, Stuart M
    - Loeb, Leo
    - Chapin, Edith
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Dexter, Frederick F
    - Smith, Edric B
    - Taylor, Herbert D
    - Robson, Stuart M
    - Conklin, Edwin G
    - Rous, Peyton
    - Lathrop, Abbie E C
    - Callender, George R
    - Gray, Mrs. Alice M
    - Stein, E
  - Laurence, William L
  - Lavarre, Jose Villar
  - Law, Lloyd W
  - Lawrence, John
  - Lawrence, E O
  - Lawrence, G H
  - Lea, J W
  - Lead Treatment (Blair Bell's Treatment)
    - Atrops, Mrs. G
    - Cortes, Carlos E
    - Ewing, James
    - Cole, Rufus I
  - Leary, Ellwood S
  - Lectures
  - Leddy, Percy Allen
    - Proctor, William
    - Paine, Charles F
    - Minot, George E
    - Murry, J Archibald
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr.
    - Bean, Marion N
  - Lederle Laboratories
  - Lee, Burton James
  - Lee, Henry
  - Leeuwenhoekvereenignig
  - Lehman, Edwin P
  - Leiby, George M
  - Leitch, Archibald
  - Lenz, Maurice
  - Lescohier, A W
  - L'Esperance, Elise
  - Letters Following Newspaper Articles
  - Leukemia - Benzol Notes
  - Levene, P A
    - World War I
  - Levin, Morton L
  - Levin, Paul
  - Levine, Michael
  - Levy, Louis
    - Smith, Edric B
  - Lewis, Mrs. Margaret Reed
  - Lewis, Richard H
    - Lewis, Mrs. Annie B
    - Baetjer, Frederick Henry
    - Brown, Thomas N
    - Finney, J M T
  - Lewis, Warren H
  - Liberty Magazine
  - Liebman, Emil
  - Lieberman, Milton M
  - Liga Contra El Cancer
    - Odio De Granda, Gustavo
  - Ligue Nationale Belge Contre le Cancer
    - Fraenkel
    - Marchal, Henri
    - Atwater, Eliot
    - Congress of Scientific and Social Campaign Against Cancer
  - Ligneris, M J A des
  - Lilly, Eli
  - Lillie, Frank R
  - Lim, Robert K S
    - Tui, Co
  - Lincoln, Asa Liggett
  - Lincoln, N Stanley
  - Linney, Blanche C
    - Hussey, R G
  - Lippincott, J.B., Co.
  - Lippincott, Stuart W
  - Littell, Robert
  - Little, Arthur D., Inc.
  - Little, Clarence Cook
    - West, C J
    - Skinker, C F
    - Little, Ralph B
    - Ewing, James
    - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Carroll, Howard R
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Snell, George D
    - Wilson, E B
    - Milligan, Mrs. H V
    - Scheele, Leonard
    - Rous, Peyton
    - Murray, William S
    - Chidester, F E
  - Little, Ralph B
  - Little, Robert Andrews
  - Liu, J Heng
    - Greene, Roger S
    - Lange, Linda B
    - Embree, Edwin R
    - Bloodgood, Joseph Colt
  - Livingston, W L
    - Peabody, Francis W
    - World War I
  - Llambes, Juan J
  - Lloyd, Mrs. Helen B
  - Locke, Edwin A
  - Lockhart-Mummery, J P
  - Loeb, Jacques
  - Loeb, Leo
    - Hooker, D R
  - Loeb, Leonard B
  - Loeb, Robert F
  - Loefer, John B
  - Lofton, William M., Jr.
  - London Conference, 1928
    - Longcope, Janet
  - Long, Perrin H
  - Longcope, Janet
    - World War I
  - Longcope, Warfield T
    - Chesney, Alan M
    - Mathew, Ed
  - Look
  - Loomis, Alfred L
  - Loomis, Helen
    - Halsted, William Stewart
    - Neill, William, Jr.
  - Lorand-Loewinger, J
    - Rhoads, C P
  - Louvain University
    - Strijcker, P J De
    - Waeyenbergh, H Van
  - Lucas, Francis F
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Luck, J Murray
  - Lucke, Baldwin
    - Harvey, E Newton
  - Lumsden, Thomas
  - Lund, Wallace
  - Lupinek, Bernard
  - Lymphocyte Monograph
    - Weed, Lewis, H
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Liu, J H
    - Rous, Peyton
    - Nakahara, Ward
    - Carrel, Alexis
  - Lynch, Clara J
    - World War I
  - Mabry, Thomas
  - Macallum, A B
  - McCain, Mildred
  - MacCallum, William G
  - McCarthy, William G
  - McCarty, Maclyn
  - McClellan, George W
    - Flinn, Waldo R
  - McClure, James G K
  - MacCullen, W G
  - McDonald, Ellice
    - Itami, Shigemitsu
  - McDonald, Mrs. Henrietta
    - Kinsella, Ralph A
    - Bartlett, Willard
    - Tupper, Paul Y
    - Maguire, Ruth W
  - McEuen, C S
  - MacEwan, Edwin J
  - MacFadyen, Douglas A
  - MacFarlane, Catharine
  - McGarrah, Gates W
  - McGrath, J J
  - McIntosh, James
  - MacKay, E M
  - MacKenzie, George D
    - World War I
  - MacKenzie, Ronald D
    - Longcope, Warfield T
    - Lewis, Mrs. Margaret
    - Weed, Lewis
    - MacCallum, W G
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Wilkie, D P D
    - Smith, Edric B
  - McLean, Franklin C
    - World War I
  - MacLean, Kenneth Sheldon
  - McLean, Richard K
  - MacLeod, Colin M
  - McLeod, James
  - McMahon, J P
  - McMurran, R L
  - McNany, Mary E
  - McNelis, John A
  - MacNider, William DeB
    - White, George
    - Richards, A N
    - Martin, William J
    - Coppridge, W illiam
  - Magnes, J L
  - Maisin, Joseph
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Galpin, Perrin C
    - Smith, Edric B
    - Spencer, R R
    - Van Zeeland, Paul
  - Major, Randolph T
  - Major, S G
  - Mall, Franklin P
  - Manchester, Mrs. Mary Margaret
  - Man-Chiang
    - Price, David E
  - Manhattan State Hospital
    - Heubel, Mrs.
  - Mann, Mrs. Lulu
  - Manning, I H
  - Mapel, C J
  - Mara, James
    - World War I
  - Maran, Mrs. Sallie E
  - March of Time
  - Marchbanks, S S
  - Marcosson, Isaac F
  - Marks, Julian D
    - World War I
  - Marquand, John
  - Marshall, B F
  - Marshall, E K, Jr.
  - Marshall, Donald Forbes
  - Marshall, Mrs. Nancy M
  - Martin
  - Martin, Franklin
  - Martin, George W
  - Martin, Hayes E
  - Martin, Solomon C
  - Marvin, Langdon P
  - Maryland Medical Journal
  - Masson, Mrs. E K
  - Masson, P
  - Mathews, Edward J
  - Mayes, J H
  - Mayneord, W V
  - Mayo, Frank
  - Mayo Clinic
    - Wilson, Lewis B
    - Wood, F C
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Desjardins, A U
  - Mead, Mrs. Elsie Cleveland
  - Meader, R G
  - Mecke, Bernard
  - Medlar, E M
  - Medrick, Raphael F
  - Meleney, Henry E
    - World War I
  - Memorial Cancer Center Fund
    - Colt, S Sloan
  - Memorial Hospital
    - Lee, Burton J
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Delafield, Edward C
    - Robbins, Harry P
    - Merriman, H Morton
    - Holmes, G F
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Petts, Ellen
    - Ladd, William
    - Smith, Homer
    - Hinsey, J C
    - Cary, Mrs. Melbert B., Jr.
    - Douglas, A
    - Kraemer, William H
    - Stewart, Fred W
    - Coombe, Reginald G
    - Marcosson, Isaac F
    - Simmons, Charles H
    - Place, Willard F
    - Howard, Frank A
    - Sloan, Alfred P., Jr.
    - Strawbridge, Robert E., Jr.
    - Pratt, Henry
    - Powelson, W V N
    - Gumbel, R W
    - Rockefeller, John D
    - Stone, William S
    - Fitzpatrick, John P
    - Fitzgerald, John P
    - Longcope, Warfield T
    - Lee, Burton J
    - Douglas, Walter
    - James, Mrs. Lucy
    - Robinson, Canby
    - Ripley, James
    - Ewing, James
    - Hayden, Charles
    - Douglas, Archibald
    - Adair, Frank E
    - Dublin, Louis
    - Cabot, Quincy S
    - Harrison, Wallace K
    - Merle-Smith, Van S
    - Greenough, Robert B
    - Ladd, William S
    - Lee, James T
    - Russell, Frederick F
    - Day, Edmund E
    - Taylor, Howard C, Jr.
    - Wallace, James L
  - Mendel, Lafayette B
  - Menkes, G
  - Merck Institute for Therapeutic Research
  - Mero-Irion, Yolanda
    - James, Henry
    - Hayes, John H
    - Russ, Inez Dane
  - Merriott, McKim
  - Metcalf, Mrs. France
  - Metherill, W A
  - Mider, G Burroughs
  - Miles, Rufus E
  - Millan, Ignacio
    - Chavez, Ignacio
  - Miller, Mrs.
    - Sullivan, T F X
  - Miller, C Phillip, Jr.
  - Miller, E C L
  - Miller, Fay
  - Miller, R B
    - World War I
  - Milligan, Mrs. Lucy R
  - Milliken, Mrs. Gerrish
  - Millman, Hyman
  - Minot, George R
  - Miscellaneous Notes
  - Missag
  - Mitchell, Edgar
  - Mitchell, Elisha, Scientific Society
    - George, W C
  - Mitchell, George A
    - Van Deusen, Edwin H
  - Mitchell, H W
  - Mixon, H J
  - Moon, Cora A
  - Moore, Emmeline
  - Moore, George E
  - Moore, Henry G
  - Moore, Sherwood
  - Morawetz, Victor
  - More, Robert H
  - Morgan, David P., Jr.
  - Morgan, Thomas Hunt
    - World War I
  - Morgenthau, Henry
  - Morin, H F
  - Moritz, Alan R
  - Morgan, Andrew
    - Clemmons, J R
    - Hayes, J H
  - Morris, Dave H
    - Auer, John
    - Kast, L
  - Morris, V N
  - Morrison, Angus W
  - Morse, Sterne
  - Morse, Sterne. A Simple Method for Anaerobic Cultivation in Petri Dishes.
  - Morton, John J
    - World War I
    - Chesney, Alan M
    - Cutler, Elliott C
    - Palmer, Walter W
    - Wearn, Joseph T
    - Avery, Oswald T
    - Chickering, Henry T
    - Dochez, A R
    - Sellards, A W
    - Swift, Homer F
    - McCann, William S
  - Moss, W L
  - Mount, Mrs. Laura
  - Mount Desert Island Hospital
    - Masterman, Ralph C
    - Holmes, Dorothy P
  - Mountain, Stephen V
  - Mueller, J Howard
  - Murlin, John R
  - Murphy, Gibbons Westbrook
  - Murphy, J.B
    - Antibody Formation
    - The Bearing of the Growth of Foreign Tissue in the Embryo on the Questions of the Heteroplastic Grafting
    - Bibliography
    - Blood Counts
    - Blood Counts on Tonsil Cases
    - Charts (Miscellany)
    - Concerning Tumor Origin
    - Concerning Tumors
    - Data for Herbert D. Taylor JEM 1919 page 41. Note Illustrious Group
    - Discussion of Certain Etiological Factors in the Causation and Transmission of Malignant Tumors
    - Discussion of Dr. Cutler's Paper
    - Discussion on Symposium on Surgery and Radiation in the Treatment of Cancer
    - Discussions of Drs. Woglom and Stevenson Papers
    - Effect of Adrenal Grafting on Transplanted Lymphatic Leukemia in Rats
    - Effect of Adrenalectomy on the White Blood Counts and Anti-Body Formation in Rabbits
    - Effect of Cellular Reaction Induced by X-Ray on the Fate of Cancer Grafts
    - Effect of Growth or Retrogression of a Transplantable Lymphosarcoma of the Rat..
    - Effect of Lymphoid Destruction on Experimental Tuberculosis in Mice
      - Ellis, Arthur W M
    - Effect of Physical Agents on the Resistance of Mice to Cancer
    - Effect of Splenectomy on the Circulating White Blood Cells of the Rat
    - Effect of X-Ray on the Resistance to Cancer in Mice
    - Experimental Studies in X-Ray Effects
    - Experiments on the Role of Lymphose Tissues in the Resistance to Experimental Tuberculosis in Mice
    - Factors in Immunity to Cancer
    - Factors of Resistance to Heteroplastic Tissue Grafting
    - Fate of Rat Tumor Growth
    - Fate of Tissue When Left in Embryo
    - Growth of Transmissable Chicken Sarcoma in Embryo
    - Heteroplastic Grafting
    - Implantation of Embryos with Tumor
    - Inhibiting Effect of Ethyl Urethane on the Development of Lymphatic Leukemia in Rats
    - Irritants as Producers of Tumors in the Embryo
    - Leukemia Strain Inhalation Results
    - The Lymphocyte as a Factor in Natural and Induced Resistance to Transplanted Cancer
    - Lymphocyte in Natural and Induced Resistance to Transplanted Cancer
    - Lymphocytes in Vitro
    - Lymphoid Tissue and Antibody Formation
    - Notes on Barnard Hospel's Lecture
    - Notes on Experiments
    - On Tumors
    - Report of a Conversation on X-Rays
    - Report on... Transplant Cancers
    - Role of Lymphocytes in Experimental Tuberculosis in Mice
    - Some Factors in the Resistance to Heteroplastic Tissue Grafting
    - Sources of Resistance to Heteroplastic Grafting
    - Speech Before AAAS, Atlantic City, 1936
    - The Stimulation and Inhibition of Tumor Growths
    - Studies in Circulating Lymphocytes
    - Studies in Lymphoic Activity
    - Studies in X-Ray Effect
    - Studies in X-Ray Effects on Cancer Immunity
    - Studies of Transplantability of Animal Tumors
    - Study of Transplantable Rat and Mouse Tumors
    - Transplantability of Malignant Tumors to the Embryos of a Foreign Species
    - Transplantability of Tissues to a Foreign Species Embryo
    - Transplantability to the Embryo of Foreign Species
    - Tumor Mouse Records
    - Ultimate Fate of Tissue Implanted in a Foreign Species Embryo
    - X-Ray Treatment in re Tonsils Flexner, Simon
    - X-Rays Effects on New Crowths of Skin
  - Murphy, J G
  - Murphy, Mrs. P L
  - Murphy, Walter
  - Murray, Mrs. Elizabeth Faison
  - Murray, William S
  - Myer, Adolf
  - Nakahara, Waro
    - Riley, William A
    - Rosenau, M J
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Kelly, Harry
    - Sams, Crawford F
    - Biasi, Margaret
    - Robbins, William Jacob
    - World War I
  - Nanee, Mollie
  - National Academy of Medicine - John J.
    - Carty Medal
    - Bowman, Isaiah
    - Jewett, Frank B
    - Vaughan, T Wayland
    - Buckley, Oliver E
    - Bush, Vannevar
    - Wright, Fred E
    - Zwemer, Raymund L
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1936-1940
    - Vigneaud, Vincent Du
    - Ward, Henry B
    - Brockett, Paul
    - Cattell, Ware
    - Rous, Peyton
    - Miner, Eunice Thomas
  - National Academy of Sciences., 1941
    - Wright, Fred E
    - Voegtlin, Carl
    - Chuvakhin, D
    - Jewett, Frank B
    - Opie, Eugene L
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1942-45
    - Opie, Eugne L
    - Goodpasture, Ernest W
  - National Advisory Cancer Council
    - Spencer, R R
    - Hektoen, Ludvig
    - Parran, Thomas
    - Smith, George M
    - Marshino, Ora
    - Voegtlin, Carl
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Dyer, R E
    - Meader, R G
  - National Advisory Cancer Council, Tenth Meeting
    - Hektoen, Ludvig
  - National Advisory Cancer Council, Eleventh Meeting
    - Cooper, William
  - National Advisory Cancer Council, Twelfth Meeting
    - Little, C C
    - Spencer, R R
    - Voegtlin, Carl
    - Hektoen, Ludvig
  - National Advisory Cancer Council - Thirteenth Meeting
    - Voegtlin, Carl
    - Kolle, Laurence
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Hektoen, Ludwig
    - Lawrence, John H
    - Little, C C
    - Thompson, L R
    - Compton, Arthur H
  - National Advisory Cancer Council - Seventeenth Meeting
    - Hektoen, Ludvig
  - National Advisory Cancer Council - Eighteenth Meeting
  - National Broadcasting Company
  - National Cancer Institute
    - Spencer, R R
    - Thompson, J W
  - National Cyclopedia of American Biography
  - National Economy Committee
    - Bernard, Pierre
    - Roosevelt, Archibald B
    - Rous, Peyton
  - National Institute of Health
    - McCoy, G W
  - National Institute of Health - Cancer, 1938
    - Bryan, Ernest R
    - Voegtlin, Carl
    - Hektoen, Ludvig
    - Reid, Mont R
    - Thompson, L R
    - Spencer, R R
    - Harrison, Ross G
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Northrop, John H
    - Little, C C
    - Parran, Thomas
    - Brake, A E
  - National Institute of Health - Cancer, 1939
    - Voegtlin, Carl
    - Bryan, Ernest R
    - Calkins, Gary N
    - Brake, A E
    - Welker, William H
    - Hektoen, Ludvig
    - Thompson, L R
    - Levine, Michael
    - Spencer, R R
    - Parran, Thomas
    - Casey, Albert E
    - Conant, James B
  - National Institute of Health - Cancer, 1940
    - Hektoen, Ludvig
    - Parran, Thomas
    - Voegtlin, Carl
    - Thibaudeau, A A
    - Draper
    - Mider, G Burroughs
    - Thompson, L C
    - Smith, G M
    - Marshino, Ora
    - Guthrie, M C
  - National Institute of Health - Cancer, 1941
    - Reid, Mont R
    - Parran, Thomas
    - Voegtlin, Carl
    - Hektoen, Ludvig
    - Doisy, E A
    - Barrett, Morris K
    - Marshino, Ora
    - Spencer, R R
  - National Institute of Health - Cancer, 1942
    - Voegtlin, Carl
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Thompson, J W
    - Barrett, Morris K
    - Nettleship, Anderson
    - Hektoen, Ludvig
  - National Research Council
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Weed, Lewis H
    - Stephenson, C S
    - Owen, Philip S
    - Berry, George
    - Gallagher, T F
    - MacEwan, Edwin J
  - Nauts, Helen Coley
  - Neal, Herbert V
  - Necheles, H
  - Neff, J Louis
  - Nelson, E W
  - Nelson, John B
  - Nettleship, Anderson
    - Ray, O M
  - Neuhof, Harold
    - Lieb, Charles Christian
  - Neumann, E O H
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1923-1928
    - Ritchie, John W
    - Cole, Rufus Ivory
    - Beekman, Fenwick
    - Williams, Linsly R
    - Reynolds, F P
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1929-1930
    - Williams, Linsly R
    - Cole, Rufus Ivory
    - Hartwell, John A
    - Cohn, Alfred E
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1930-1932
    - Williams, Linsley L
    - Corwin, E H L
    - Cole, Rufus Ivory
    - Reynolds, Frederick P
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Ebeling, Albert H
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1936-1940
    - Reznikoff, Paul
    - Warburton, Gladys
    - Hajek, Joseph
    - Medical Society of New York
    - Williams
    - Lambert, Samuel W
    - Hyams, Joseph A
    - Doan, Charles A
    - Hamilton, B W
    - Wilcox, Herbert B
    - Scott, James Ralph
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1949
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Committee on Public Relations, 1926-1931
    - Corwin, E H Lewrinski
    - Miller, James Alexander
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Joint Committee with New York State Board of Charities, 1928
    - Lawrence, Joseph S
    - Ford, C E
    - Johnson, Charles
    - Burritt, Bailey B
    - Swope, Gerard
    - Corwin, E H L
    - Hayes, Hannah F
    - Savage, P G
    - Stewart, W R
    - Williams, Linsly R
  - New York Academy of Sciences.
    - Gordon, Myron
  - New York City Cancer Committee
    - Kilpatrick, John Reed
  - New York Hospital
  - New York Medical Journal
  - New York Medical Week
  - New York State Civil Service Commission
    - Birdseye, John C
  - New York Times
    - Winter, Norman
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Markel, Lester
    - Hayward, Walter B
  - Newell, John P
  - Newman, Augusta
    - Lee, Burton J
    - Newman, Hugo
    - Pack, George T
  - Ney, H
  - Nicholson, Hayden C
    - Poteat, Douglass
    - Hauck, James S
  - Nielson, Jens
  - Nixon, P Ireland
  - Nobel Prize Committee
    - Johansson, J E
  - Noble, R L
  - Noel, R
  - Nordoff, Paul
  - Norris, Charles
  - North Carolina Society of New York
    - Patterson, Rufus L
  - Northrop, John H
  - Norwood, Robert
  - Noyons, A K
  - Nunez Grimaldos, Joaquin
    - World War I
  - Nye, Robert N
  - Oberling, Charles
  - Oberndorf, C P
  - O'Brien, Daniel P
  - O'Brien, John J
  - O'Connor, Hugh
  - O'Donoghue, William
  - Ogata, T
  - Oglethorpe University
    - Jacobs, Thornwell
    - Stovall, M E
    - Peters, T K
    - Little, Clarence Cook
    - Hopper, W Earl
  - O'Grady, Mrs. Flora H
  - Oliver, Lorimer R
  - Olmsted, B
  - Olsen, Mrs.
    - Auchincloss, Hugh
  - O'Neill, John J
  - Ordway, Thomas
  - O'Rourke, Mary
  - Osterhout, Winthrop J V
  - Otis, Herbert Foster
  - Oughterton, A W
  - Owen, Clarence I
  - Owen, Philip S
    - Heston, W E
  - Pack, George T
  - Packard, Arthur W
  - Packchanian, Ardzroony
  - Page, Irvine H
  - Paget, Muriel
  - Pallade, George Emil
  - Palmer, Walter W
  - Pan American Airways, Inc.
  - Pan American Medical Association
    - Duff, John
    - Caldwell, George W
    - Eller, Joseph Jordan
    - Quick, Douglas
    - Ernst, Edwin C
  - Parfentjev, I A
  - Park, Edwards A
  - Parker, Elmer L
  - Parker, F, Jr.
    - Auger, Carlton
  - Parsons, A L
  - Parsons, S T
  - Passey, R D
  - Paterson, Ralston
  - Pattee, Eunice H
    - Bumgardner, Eugenia
  - Paul, John R
  - Pauli, Wolfgang F
  - Paulson, Avis
  - Pawan, J L
  - Payne, Bruce R
    - Adair, Fred
  - Payne, George C
  - Peabody, Francis W
    - World War I
  - Peabody, F W - Blood Counts
    - Livingston, W K
  - Pearce, Louise
    - Conner, C L
  - Pearce, Richard M
    - World War I
  - Pearlman, Robert M
  - Pearsall, Kate
  - Pearson Foundation
  - Peerless, J
  - Peller, S
  - Pentz, Peggy
  - Person, Mrs. W M
  - Perkins, Richard R
  - Peters, Guy M
    - Elworth, James E
  - Petillo, Diomede
  - Petrazelka, Charles
  - Pfahler, G E
  - Phifer, E W
  - Phillips, Charles
  - Pickering, Dr.
  - Pierce, Ethel Girdwood
  - Pierson, Richard N
  - Pijoan, Michel
    - Blake, Francis G
    - Pijoan, Joseph
  - Pillsbury, H C
  - Piper, Stanley E
  - Pischel, Mrs.
    - Corscaden, J A
  - Pitts, Herman C
    - Charlton, H R
  - Plague Organism
    - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr.
    - Armstrong, Charles
  - Plasencia, Leonel
  - Pomeroy, L A
  - Pool, John
    - Bayne-Jones, S
  - Poor [?], Eva Katie
  - Pope, Arthur
  - Porter, Emily A
  - Porter, Keith R
    - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Bray, Harry N
  - Porter, William B
  - Post, E R
  - Post, Edward Everett
  - Potter, James S
  - Poultry Research Laboratory
    - Wintan, Berley
    - Rhoads, Cornelius P
    - Waters, Nelson F
  - Pourbaix, Yvonne
  - Powell, Garfield
  - Prest, John D
  - Price, Winston H
  - Prickett, C O
  - Proctor, William
  - Prudden, Lillian E
  - Prudden, T M
    - World War I
  - Pulvirenti, Francesco
  - Pund, Edgar R
  - Pusey, William Allen
  - Pyle, Charles McAlpin
  - Quick, Douglas
    - Weir, Mrs. Margaret Bronson
  - Rackemann, Francis M
    - Rackemann, Felix
  - Radioactive Isotopes
  - Radiological Society of North America
    - Williams, Alden
  - Rand, Frederick V
  - Rand, James H., Jr.
    - Rand, James H., III
    - Rumely, Edward A
  - Raines, Caroline Parker
  - Ravenel, Leonard J
  - Ray, O M
    - Strong, Leonell C
  - Read, Florence M
    - Hackett, L W
    - Russell, Frederick F
  - Red Cross - see: American Red Cross
    - World War I
  - Reding, R
  - Regaud, Claude
  - Reich, William Walter
  - Reichert, Philip
  - Reid, Howard
  - Reid, J
  - Reid, Mont R
  - Reimann, Stanley P.
  - Reisner, Gerald S
  - Report on the Research of the Department of Anatomy [John Hopkins Medical School].
  - Reprint Requests and Acknowledgements
  - Reprint - Theories and Cures
  - Requests for Animals and Materials
    - Wuerthele - Cospe, Virginia
    - Bass, Allan D
    - Greenstein, Jesse P
    - Begg, R W
    - Carson, J R
    - Brunschwig, Alexander
    - Thompson, J W
    - Grand, C G
    - Sturm, Ernest
    - Chambers, Robert
    - Schrek, Robert
    - Sugarbaker, Everett D
    - Gurchot, Charles
    - Melnick, Perry J
    - Bela, Kellner
    - Dudley, H C
    - Jackson, Harold
    - Smith, Marcus J
    - Citron, Robert R
    - Sellei, Camillo
    - Greenspan, Ezra M
    - Law, Lloyd W
    - Nelson, Robert A., Jr.
    - Stasney, Joseph
    - Troch
    - Potter, Michael
    - Ingle, Dwight J
    - Higgins, George M
  - Reviews
  - Reynolds, H C
  - Rhoads, Cornelius P
    - Robbins, Harry P
    - Abels, Jules C
    - Baumann, C A
    - Dobriner, Konard
    - Gallagher, T F
    - Tagnon, H J
    - Chanutin, Alfred
    - Solomons, Bethel
  - Rhodes, Goodrich B
  - Rice, A T
  - Rice, John L
  - Rich, Mrs. Ellen
  - Richards, Alfred N
    - National Academy of Science
  - Richards, Mrs. Anna M
    - Westfalt, J V E
  - Riddell, W A
  - Ridder, Victor F
  - Ridmond, Roland L
  - Rieber, Willy K
  - Riegel, Byron
  - Rinehart, Stanley M., Jr.
  - Ripley, James H
    - Wilson, E B
  - Risley, Dora E
  - Rivers, Thomas M